Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 78, Folder: 16 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 42: Service Sponsor Course, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 43: Arbitration between United Retail, Wholesale and Dept. Store Employees (C.I.O.) and its Local 1-S and R.H. Macy and Co., INC, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 44: Senior Executive Training Course, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. 2 copies. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Dear Friend and Member of Local 1-S, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By Sam Kovenetsky. Letter to employees. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Macy's Medical Department: Examination of Applicant, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 47: Personnel Division: Employment Department, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 48: Macy's To Test Drivers, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By New York Times. November 6, 1927. Newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Macy 25-Year Club Dines, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By New York Times. November 29, 1928. Newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Girl Wins Macy Prizes, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By New York Times. January 27, 1928. Newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Employment Physical Record, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 52: Medical Treatment (continued), Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By R.H. Macy and Co. Continuation sheet for medical card. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Macy Mutual Aid Association: Ear, Nose and Throat Service, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 54: Macy Mutual Aid Association: Sick Report, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 55: Non-Selling Rating: Department of Training, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 56: Personality Study Card, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 57: Daily Report: Employment Interviewer, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 58: Daily Report: Rail Interviewer, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 59: Examination of Foodhandler, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 60: Periodic Examination, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 61: Week's Leave of Absence, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 62: Sent Home By Hospital, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 63: Macy Workers Rewarded, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By R.H. Macy and Co. April 26, 1929. newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Certificate of taxpayer, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By NYS Department of Taxation. Blank form 101. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Certificate of Non-Residence, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By NYS Department of Taxation. Blank form 102. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Signiture Card, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 67: Macy's Training Squad Application, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 68: Brisco, Morris A. Store Manager, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By R.H. Macy and Co. handwritten notes. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Benefits chart, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By R.H. Macy and Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Entitled to Nourishment, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 71: Kindly report to the Macy Mutual Aid Association, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 72: Reported Illness, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 73: Application for Training Squad, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 74: Application for Training Squad, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 75: Training Squad Study, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 76: Certificate of Alien Claiming Residence, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By Treasury Department. Blank form 1078. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Pass To Leave Building, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 78: Hospital Record, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 79: Dental Office Appointment, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 80: Budget Form, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 81: Salesforce Budget, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 82: Personnel Record, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By R.H. Macy and Co. 10 Blank personnel forms. Item is in English.
  - Item 83: Macy's Executive Training Squad, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Item 84: Macy's Store Signs With A C.I.O. Union, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By New York Times. December 23, 1937. Newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
  - Item 85: Medical Plan At Macy's, Publication (Box 78, Folder 16)
    By New York Times. August 11, 1949. Newspaper clipping. Item is in English.
- Box: 78, Folder: 17 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Plan for Part-Payment of Tuition Policy, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Executive Training Department Section Head Course, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Training Squad Conference Notes, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Program For Training Employment Interviewees, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Interviewer Training Demonstration Interview, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Interviewer Training Conference I, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Review: Knowledge Required and Sources From Previous Conference, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Interviewer Training Conference IV, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Interviewer Training Conference V, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Section Head Training Program, Publication (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Box: 78, Folder: 18 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Selling Cosmetics, Publication (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Miscellaneous System Training Procedures, Publication (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Box: 78, Folder: 19 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Agreement between R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Local 1-S of the Retail Wholesale and Department Store Employees Union, C.I.O, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Your Opportunities are greater Your Future more interesting with Macy's, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: A Simplified Guide for Shop Stewards To the Local 1-S Unaffiliated Contract for 1949-1950, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
    By Local 1-S. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Color, Line, and Design, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Color, Line, and Design for Fashion Departments, Publication (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Box: 78, Folder: 20 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Macy's Heath Plan for Exempt Staff Employees, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Retirement System For Employees of R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Affiliates, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. January 24, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Little Mis'Hap speaks, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Olan, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: Retirement system For Employees of R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Affiliates, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. January 7, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Your Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: The Health Plan sponsored by Local1-S Unaffiliated and Macy's New York, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Information for Employes, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Blue Cross Hospital Plan and The Doctor's Plan For Our Employees, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Information for the Use of Non-Selling Employes, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: Announcement of Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Department of Training Organization Chart, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: The Problem Employee, His Study and Treatment, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
    By V.V. Anderson, M.D. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Non-Selling Personnel Review Rating Sheet, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 16: Employment Form, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 17: Decision and Order Statement in the Matter of R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, Local 1-S, C.I.O., Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
    By State Labor Relations Board. January 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Personnel Record: 3082, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
    By Manufacturers Hanover Trust. Blank personnel form. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Officier Appraisal, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 20: Officier Appraisal: Metropolitan Division, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Item 21: Officier Appraisal: Operations Division, Publication (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Box: 78, Folder: 21 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Camp Isidia, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Macy Mutual Aid Association Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. August 24th, 1924. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Information for Staff Members, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: The College Graduate in Retailing, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: System Book for Macy Salesclerks, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Collective Bargaining Agreement between Macy's New York and Local 1-S Retail, Wholesale, Department Store Workers Union, A.F.L.-C.I.O, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. April 1, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Collective Bargaining Agreement between Macy's New York and Macy Department Store Employees Union, Local 1-S Unaffiliated, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. November 1, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Taking the "Yarn" Out of Selling Sweaters, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: How To Sell Negligees, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Contract between R.H. Macy and Co., INC Selling Division and the Local 1, Store Division URWDSEA, CIO., Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. March 4, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: System Book for Macy Salesclerks, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: Retirement System For Employees of R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Affiliates, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. October 21, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Retirement System For Employees of R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Affiliates, Publication (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Box: 79, Folder: 1 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Department Stores Organizing Committee, C.I.O. and the Macy Chapter (Local No. 1), Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. April 4, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement between R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Department Stores Organizing Committee C.I.O., Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Macy Chapter (Local 1) of the Department Stores Organizing Committee, Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. April 4, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Salesclerks' Orientation, Publication (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Box: 79, Folder: 2 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Service Sponsor Conference Outline, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Retirement system for Employees of R.H. Macy and Co., INC and Affiliates, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Macy Mutual Aid Association Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. August 4, 1924. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Macy Mutual Aid Association Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
    By R.H. Macy and Co., INC. February 1, 1921. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Handbook for Members of the Macy Mutual Aid Association, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Annual Report, Publication (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Box: 79, Folder: 3 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Annuities and Benefits, Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
    By Magnolia Petroleum Co. July 1, 1918. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report of Conference on Improving Foremanship, Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
    By Magnolia Petroleum Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report of Conference on Improving Foremanship, Publication (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Box: 79, Folder: 4 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: What the Maine Supervisor Should Know About Grievance Procedures, Publication (Box 79, Folder 4)
    By Maine Office of Employee Relations. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 5 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: In The Mainstream Volume 2, Number 3, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
    By Mainstream Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: In the Mainstream Volume 2, Number 2, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: In the Mainstream Volume 1, Number 1, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: In The Mainstream Volume 1, Number 3, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: In the Mainstream Volume 2, Number 1, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: In the Mainstream Volume 1, Number 2, Publication (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Box: 79, Folder: 6 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Cooperative Savings for Retirement Program, Publication (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Box: 79, Folder: 7 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: If A Union Organizer Calls, Publication (Box 79, Folder 7)
    By Management Information Center, INC. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How To Negotiate a Workable Labor Agreement, Publication (Box 79, Folder 7)
    By Hans a. Feldman. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 8 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Automation And Electronics, A guide to Company Experience, Publication (Box 79, Folder 8)
    By Henry C. Thole. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 9 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 9)
    By Management Research Services. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 10 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution, Publication (Box 79, Folder 10)
    By Manufacturers Club of Bloomfield. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 11 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 11)
    By Manufacturers Association of Bridgeport, Connecticut. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 12 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Preamble Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 12)
    By Manufacturers Association of Jamestown, New York. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 13 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 13)
    By Manufacturers Association of Meriden. January 6, 1944. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 14 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 14)
    By Manufacturers Association of Montgomery, PA. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 15 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Summary of Survey-Labor Status, Industrial Relations and Wage Practices, Publication (Box 79, Folder 15)
    By N.H. Manufacturers Association. December 23, 1946. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 16 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Constitution, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. October, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. November 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Monthly bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. February 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. March 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. May 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. June 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. July 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. October 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. December 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. January 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. February 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. March 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. April 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. May 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. June 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. September 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. October 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. November 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. December 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. January 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. February 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. March 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. April 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. May 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. June 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. October 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. November 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. December 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. January 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. February 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. February 8, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. March and April 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. May 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 79, Folder 16)
    By Manufacturers Association of Syracuse, INC. June 1956. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 17 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: By-Laws, Publication (Box 79, Folder 17)
    By The Manufacturers Association of York, Pennsylvania. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 18 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Membership Book, Publication (Box 79, Folder 18)
    By Manufacturers' Association of Robes, Leisurewear, Shirts and Rainwear, INC. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 19 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
    By Manufacturers Hanover Trust. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Permanent Reference of Staff Benefits and Responsibilities, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Blue Cross Blue Shield Benefits, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Retirement System, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Modern Pension Plans, Publication (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Box: 79, Folder: 20 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Orientation Check List and Month Progress Report, Publication (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Box: 79, Folder: 21 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Washington News Letter For Manufacturers, Publication (Box 79, Folder 21)
    By Manufacturers News Bureau INC. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 22 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
    By Marathon Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Auto Insurance Form, Publication (Box 79, Folder 22)
    By Marathon Corporation. Blank form. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 23 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Double Challenge: Marathon oil Company and Financial Analysts, Publication (Box 79, Folder 23)
    By Marathon Oil Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 24 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 79, Folder 24)
    By Marine Terminals Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 25 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Report of Foremanship Conference, Publication (Box 79, Folder 25)
    By Marland Oil Co. March 7-20 1927. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 26 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Statement of W.A. Wecker, President of Marquette Cerement Manufacturing Company, Before The Trade Policies Committee of The United States Senate, Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
    By Marquette Cements. November 19, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Marquette's President Talks to Organized Labor, Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
    By Marquette Cements. September 12, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report To The Investor In Mr. Marquette's One-Man Cement Company, Publication (Box 79, Folder 26)
    By Marquette Cements. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 27 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The Social Gospel in Action, Publication (Box 79, Folder 27)
    By Cornell University, ILR School. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 28 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Employee Publications Handbook, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
    By Marshall field and Co. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Pension Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: You and Your Job, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Marshall Field Company and You, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Work Simplification, the Patter for Improving Work Methods, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
    By Marshall field and Co. March 11, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Supervisor's Manual Employee Performance Review, Publication (Box 79, Folder 28)
    By Marshall field and Co. July 1, 1944. Item is in English.
- Box: 79, Folder: 29 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Rate your Team, Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)
    By Glenn L. Martin Co. SuperVision no.3 (1943:Aug. 25). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 79, Folder 29)